

## Mai Tran Nguyen An

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Career Summary: More than 3 years experienced web developer with the track record of progress in fast paced and complex business environment. Exceptionally organizational and planning skills with the ability to work under pressure skills and outstanding team building and client satisfaction. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and can communicate clearly and effectively. Currently looking for a opportunity to join a dynamic, ambitious, growing company and forge a career as a first class website developer.

Key Skills:

Professional

Experience:

- Solid web development experience using PHP, MySQL, Smarty, AJAX, HTML5, CSS3, XML and JavaScript/jQuery
- Knowledge of Responsive Web Design.
- Building large scale ecommerce websites with CMS systems.
- Building Android App.
- Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe Illustrator, Sublime Text, Android Studio.
- Excellent attention to detail both front and back end.
- Exceptionally good communication skills with the strong problem solving and troubleshooting skills.
- Able to clearly communicate technical data to non technical clients.

Web Developer – Team Leader Derasoft Co., Ltd Tan Binh Dicstrict, Ho Chi Minh City May 2015 – Present

- Lead team of 4 staffs.
- Mentoring and training up junior and new staff.
- Developing enterprise CMS systems.
- Creating websites that are user-friendly, effective and appealing
- Producing, modifying and maintaining websites and web applications.
- Testing a website, identifying bugs and technical problems.
- Meeting with customers and end users to analyse their needs.
- Maintain the account of performance issues and developed complex database components.
- Writing support documentation and provided training to internal and external users.
- Resolve problems of production by working with the end-users.

Android Developer
Derasoft Co., Ltd
Tan Binh Dicstrict, Ho Chi Minh City
May 2014 - August 2014

- Created 3 fully functional applications for Android devices.
- Wrote clean, clear, efficient, well-tested, and maintainable code.

Web Developer
Derasof Co., Ltd
Tan Binh Dicstrict, Ho Chi Minh City
May 2012 - April 2015

- Translate designs to front-end code, estimate time and costs, and determine developer requirements and specifications.
- Developing enterprise CMS systems.

### Porfilo

### Check my online porfilo

# Educational qualifications:

Bachelor of Science with Credit, Electronics - Telecommunication, University of Natural Sciences, Ho Chi Minh City

### Contact

Mobile: 0169 208 1649

Email: an.maitrannguyen@gmail.com

Address: 256/4, Tan Phuoc Street, Ward 6, District 10, Ho Chi Minh City

### References

Available on request